Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you!
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see!
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in wonderland.
Princess Vivi.
You see, this desert
is where. Ah! You die!
Potter!
Oh, no.
You see, you two can't get away, swan!
You hear me?
There's no escape for you!
Just give up now! Okay?
I'm going to trample you both
with all the grace of a ballerina!
Cotton!
You saved my life!
You're in no shape to be
running like this now!
No!
If you go straight, we'll
be cornered on the stairway!
Folks, listen to me!
Just give it up and stop right there!
Let me off here!
I'm going to fight him!
What are you doing?
That way's a cliff!
You can't be serious!
That duck is actually running
up the sheer face of a cliff?
Dumb duck! Nice try,
but now you'll fall back down here and
my ballet Kenpo will finish you off!
How'd he do that?
Karoo, that's amazing! You flew!
Surely Mr.
Two won't be able to
follow us at this point.
That was a cute little
move, Duck, but it's no use!
There's nothing I can't do!
With the help of my incredible ballet
compo, I can renovate right up this cliff!
Arun, do you think you can make
it through the battlefield?
We'll never be able to find
Koza in all this confusion,
so we'll look for Chaka instead.
We need to reach the royal palace.
And we have to make it before the rebel
army reaches the center of the city.
We must!
Oh my!
I'm here!
A straight bullet, oh no!
Karoo!
Phoebe is our friend too, Kokoro!
Gotcha!
Karoo!
Just give up!
I told you, it's no use!
All right.
Stay out of my way, Dock!
And maybe you won't get hurt, okay?
I...
WAAAAAAA! No, stop!
It's you guys.
Nice work there, Captain Karoo.
You did a damn good job.
Oh Sanji you're here.
At ease ducks.
You can stand down.
Now Vivi?
Don't you have a rebellion to stop?
Go on.
I'll take care of this creep.
So I take it you're that
ridiculous face changing freak huh?
You really should stay out of my way!
But first, just who are you?
Go on.
You guys, watch Karoo.
Oh, no!
She's getting away!
Oh, you gotta be kidding me!
Give me a break here!
Well, now you get to die!
I think I'll get started by having you
return our sharp-shoots prized goggles.
And that's just the beginning. Huh?
Hope you didn't think I would
be as easy to beat as him.
You're with the Straw Hats, huh?
Well, then, that must make
you the mysterious prince.
My name is Sanji, and I'm the
best cook in the entire ocean.
Cook?
I happen to be a super
first-class top-rate cook as well.
But I use my skills to support an underworld
organization, not some useless kingdom.
You're not the only one
who knows the underworld.
I happen to be a cook and a pirate.
Hmm.
Well, then, this should
be quite interesting.
I'll make this clear.
Keep your hands off this country.
Chopper!
Hey, Chopper!
Come on, wake up!
Open your eyes!
Oh, Usopp, it looks like you're all right.
That's great.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're the one we need to worry about.
No, it isn't serious.
So, this is all that's left of the Mr.
Four pair, huh?
And here I came to help you.
I, the great Captain Usopp,
the champion of the seas,
the hero of the world, was going
to demonstrate my fighting skills.
by bravely coming to a friend's rescue.
Be careful.
They're still here waiting for us.
What?
Why didn't you say so?
What was that?
How did that happen?
There's no one even out there.
That's because they're underground.
Miss Merry Christmas ate the mole mole
Devil Fruit and now she's a mole woman.
A mole woman?
The other one, Mr.
Four, is a fourth batter
and his dog's the pitcher.
What?
None of that Jabra jabber made any sense!
What the hell does it mean?
Look out!
Four!
Are you okay, Lusop?
Man, that was really close.
I'm glad you were there, Chopper.
What exactly was that thing, anyway?
Like I said, that's Mr. Four's thing.
He's a fourth batter.
He works together with his dog.
Which brings me back to my earlier point.
None of that makes any sense.
Ha!
Look, he's over there!
Huh?
A dog?
Gah!
What is that weird thing?
That's not good. What? Huh? What's that?
Gah!
Here it comes! Not good!
Usopp, you have to get
away from there, quickly!
Hurry, now!
Usopp, no!
Are you all right, Usopp?
Okay, one more time.
What is that?
The ball is a time bomb and explodes when
it's set to whether or
not it hits anything.
Basically, Mr.
Fork can calculate the time
needed and then hit the ball.
The ball will then explode
when its time is up.
I tried to catch one before it
exploded and throw it back at him,
but it's as heavy as a wrecking ball.
There's no way to catch it,
and it's impossible to throw.
The fact that Mr.
Fork can hit it with a bat at the
speed he does is absolutely incredible.
His strength is extraordinary.
It's beyond anything
I've ever seen before.
That bat of his just
knocked down a brick wall.
How much could that thing possibly weigh?
Hey, Mr. Four! Mr. Four!
What are you doing, moron?
You moron!
Go and get him instead
of just standing there.
Come on, let him have it already. Go now!
Go on, moron!
Kill him!
Smoke him!
Moron! Moron! Run!
Run!
Now! Do it now!
Over there, it's the mole woman.
She is a mole woman!
I haven't even changed yet!
You moron, you moron!
Chopper, you'll have to take it from here.
Do me a favor and have my body buried
and see what I've gone okay on.
You cowardly jerk!
You just got done saying
you had come here to help!
Look here, you!
How do you expect me to fight
against a freaky muscle man,
his weird dog-gun
hybrid, and a mole woman?
There's no way!
I'm a human.
Do you think you can understand that?
I'm a human too, jerk!
No, you're not.
You're a big furry monster.
What about you?
Have you seen that nose of yours?
Anyway, his name is Lasso.
He's a gun that ate the dachshund
variety of the mutt-mutt fruit.
Are we clear?
Let me get this straight.
Are you saying that a
gun ate a Devil Fruit?
It's a new technique
here on the Grand Line.
Even inanimate objects
can eat a Devil Fruit.
Ha!
You call that lying?
If he was originally a gun,
how could he eat anything?
A gun can't even move on its own.
You're just making all of
this up, you mole-woman!
Shut up!
It's top secret anyway, and I wouldn't have
told you except for you're going to die.
A gun can't help it if it moves.
So there, there, there, there!
So there!
Now isn't that right, Mr.
Four?
Mm-hmm.
Anyway, like I was saying,
you're gonna die here.
You have no hope of escaping now
that you've entered our territory.
No, nuh-uh.
No hope at all.
You should enjoy this.
Welcome to a territory we
call Mole Hill Block 4.
Look!
Now she's turning into a
mole-woman thing for real!
A penguin? A penguin! I'm a mole!
Now you shut up!
She's underground!
Now's my chance!
Wait, hey!
You can handle it from here, I'm sure!
Watch out, who's up!
It's missed!
Close! Four!
Oh no!
Usopp, look, it's above you! Huh?
It's a fly ball! Ha!
No problem!
Looks like their cleanup batter
can't clean up very well, huh?
How sad!
I can dodge this one with my eyes closed!
Spinball!
Look out behind you!
He's fourth in our lineup
for a reason, moron!
You haven't seen anything yet!
They're over there!
How did you two have the time to move?
You changed form!
All right, so you're a zon-type!
And I was thinking you were just
a normal person all this time!
Usopp, we have no choice
but to keep moving.
If we stop for a second, we're dead.
I get it.
If we stand still, then we're just
sending ducks for them to keep firing at.
Here they come!
If I can get to that guy
and knock him down...
Just hold on!
The game isn't going to be any fun
if we don't have a batter, now is it?
Jumper!
Oh, well, at least I can still do that.
Huh?
Dare we mole?
That's it!
Damn.
If they keep running away through these
mole tunnels, even if I use a rumble ball?
I won't have enough time
to do any real damage.
Hey.
Where is he?
We're missing one of them!
Where's the ugly guy with
the long nose we're off to?
Where is he?
Where?
Yeah, I don't see Usopp around anywhere.
What's the matter?
You guys lose something?
Where are you?
Where did you go?
Wait, is he?
Yeah, so kind of you to dig
all these tunnels, really.
You do realize,
though, that you're not the only one
who can crawl around inside of them.
Usopp!
You sneaky little rat!
You were hiding in one of the holes!
Whoa!
Mr. Fork!
What?
It looks like he's
using a five-ton hammer!
How does a string bean like him
have the strength to do that?
That's a big hammer.
Who exactly is this long-nosed freak?
I am a traveler of the world's oceans,
a crusher of notorious monsters, beasts,
and foes, a sinker of countless ships,
a flattener of numberless
towns, trembling with fear.
People everywhere call me
the master of destruction.
I suggest that you take the time
to remember my name carefully.
I am Captain Usopp!
Wow, wow, wow!
Awesome, awesome, awesome!
Yes, yes, thank you very much.
That's nothing really.
I'll be signing autographs later.
That was amazing.
I thought you were useless up until now.
Hey!
Mr. Thor!
He isn't moving.
Could I really hit him that hard?
No, it doesn't matter.
This is my chance to beat them both.
I have to take it.
Your turn, Penguin!
Now you'll feel the wrath
of my five-ton hammer!
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Face my ooze up!
Down!
She escaped.
Where are you, Penguin?
I told you I'm a mole,
not a Penguin, moro!
Now I see you!
Rubber baby boom.
Damn!
You're everywhere, mole-woman!
Ha!
Hey, you missed me, so what's
the point of that big hammer?
If you can't manage to hit me!
Let me tell you something, Penguin.
I'm sure you've heard by now
that a good number of your
fellow Baroque Works agents
have been eliminated by us.
But the truth is, it was all me. No!
You did all that!
In addition to that, I command 8,000 men!
That's awesome!
Five tons! Awesome! Five tons! Awesome!
Five tons! Awesome!
He has to wake up now?
He survived being hit
by a five-ton hammer?
What kind of monster is he?
Yeah, he doesn't even
have a bump on his head!
He took a direct blow to the head
from a five-ton hammer, and he's okay?
Why is that?
You mean that thing was
a fake this whole time?
Of course it was!
You think I can really lift five tons?
I stopped trying after just ten pounds!
This is a model I made!
It's only a couple of frying pans tied
to a stick and covered with paper.
Why, you!
You tricked me with a piece of paper!
No more mercy for you!
Mole swimming! Mole fishing!
She's gone underground into
the mole tunnels again!
Watch out for the holes, chopper!
What's she planning this time?
Moving around underground is just
like swimming in a pool to me!
You can't escape this time!
Pool?
Now this is bad.
Oh, no! What's up?
Mr. Four! Lasso!
Go ahead and take care of that
reindeer man over there, would ya?
Let's show them your 400 base knocks!
It's no use.
There's no way I can
handle an attack like this.
It's all or nothing now.
I have to think up a way to beat this guy.
And quickly, before he kills us both!
Rumble!
Brain pulling!
Let's go!
Where's Chopper?
Chopper.
You don't have time to be
worried about someone else!
Here comes my mole banana!
Hey now! What are you doing?
It's poor form to go
after that spot on a guy!
Stop your whining!
You're alive, aren't ya?
Mole banana!
Perfect.
There's part of a wall there.
If I keep running at this
speed and she follows me,
she'll run into the part of
the wall that's under the sand.
And she'll crash really hard, too.
Banana! Banana!
Now it's time to split your
head in two, stupid penguin!
What's up?
Four...
Yeah.
Got crushed, huh?
Well, it serves you right,
you stupid old penguin woman!
I'm a mole!
I'm a mole, you moron!
Ah!
Go to the highway!
Oh, come on!
Oh, what are you doing? Let me go!
Stop it already!
This is too dangerous to do out here!
If you're not careful,
we'll run into something!
Ah!
Like that wall in front of you!
Look ahead! A wall! A wall! No!
I'm too young to die!
Oh, mole in bed!
Ah!
I got it!
I see your weakness now! Oh?
Ooh!
Usopp!
Usopp, can you get up?
Come on, Usopp!
Stay away from the fall
in all the halls, too!
You don't have to tell
me twice, I'm going!
Hurry up!
What exactly are those morons doing now?
What's that?
And that's the molehill's weakness.
All of the tunnels are connected
to each other in one big network.
Oh?
Yeah?
They're alive!
This isn't good.
My Rumble Ball's effectiveness
is already half gone by now!
No more! Huh?
No more of this!
I don't want to die in this place!
Usopp, wait!
No way!
I'm out of here!
I've had it!
There's no way to beat these two!
Not when they're still
alive after that explosion!
Running away from them isn't going
to do any good, don't you see?
Usopp!
The blue nose is right, you know!
That was quite a little stunt, you bull!
After doing something like that,
we're not gonna just let you
run away like nothing happened!
Oh no, Lucy!
Well,
I guess with the captain
who's so pathetic,
it's no surprise that the
rest of the crew's useless.
Captain?
Wait, are you...
are you talking about Luffy?
If you're talking about the Straw Hat Kid,
that idiot was killed a
little while ago by the boss.
What a shocker.
And now the rebellion has
started and is well underway.
Well, I guess you picked the
wrong people to mess with.
She said Luffy is dead.
Don't you dare lie to us!
Don't lie to us, you dirty mole woman!
We aren't gonna listen to you!
There's no way Luffy can be dead!
Do you hear me?
He'd never lose to that alligator bastard!
And what makes you think
that scrawny little captain
of yours can even last five
seconds against our boss,
you stupid long nose?
Because someday he's going to
become the king of the pirates.
So there's no chance that he
would let himself die here.
Did you hear that, Mr. Four?
He'll be the pirate king.
Pie king, pie king.
That's the stupidest
thing I've ever heard.
I have...
King of the pirates!
Only idiots like you and
your pathetic friends
will believe a ridiculous story like that!
I'm glad that pathetic
captain of yours is dead!
He was a moron who didn't
know his own place!
He was a rod!
A rod!
Jumper, listen!
A real man?
It's about time you died, long-nosed!
Hill Highway!
Listen to me, a real man,
no matter how terrifying or hideous
or corrupt his enemy might be!
I'll see you in hell,
Ron, you long-nosed Ron!
Oh, no, him back!
You okay?
No, no matter.
How's live the chance a
real man will still fight?
Mr. Four!
You're up!
Now take your betting stance!
Ready your four-ton bet!
This is it!
Mole hill!
Intersection number four!
Gah!
What's up now?
The waker always weak, even
if they pretend they're not!
How sad!
Damn you!
What did you do to him?
There are times when a real
man must stay and fight
instead of running, no matter what.
You're still standing?
Like now.
When a friend's true dream is
laughed at by someone No way!
You were hit in the head with a bat that
weighs four tons You shouldn't
even be alive, you damn Ron!
You shouldn't, no you shouldn't,
shouldn't even be alive,
no way What sort of sneaky trick
are you using this time, huh?
Luffy is not dead.
He's going to be King
of the Pirates someday!
I know he will!
That is one day that I will never
let you laugh at! Never! Ha!
I guess the Long Nose hasn't
learned his lesson yet.
Let's go again, Mr.
Firehorn!
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Let me show you the transformation
point I've been saving.
Porn point!
I'm coming, stop!
You get an A for determination,
but no matter how hard you try,
you'll have no chance of defeating me!
Jumper!
Jumper, just get behind me, okay?
Yeah, got it!
All right, Mr.
Ford, get ready!
Take this special attack.
Now here we go! All here!
Special attack booster!
All right, Chopper, the rest is up to you!
Right.
That stupid brat took up his
shoes and jumped right off!
Down no hill!
Intersection number four!
No, don't do it, Mr.
Moore!
Don't do it!
Hey, you guys!
Why don't you take a look over here?
Now, Usopp jump or attack!
Hammer Comet!
We did it.
Are you okay?
Usopp, just hang in there, all right?
Don't die on me!
We need to find a doctor!
A doctor!
That's you.
Oh, yeah.